(Howard(translating for Emily):)I think I wrote a letter to Santa Claus
every day.
(Howard(translating for Emily):)And then on Christmas morning...
(Howard(translating for Emily):)...under the tree is a little puppy
with a red ribbon.
- What are you doing?
- Texting Bernadette I'm gonna be late.
- Dude, what is she saying?
- It's a funny story about a puppy.
(Howard:)Just smile and laugh.
(Howard:)- Quick, stop smiling.
- What? Why?
(Howard:)The puppy died. It choked
on a doll head. Sad face, sad face.
(Raj:)It's a little hard to see
with the city lights...
(Raj:)...but that W-shaped constellation
is Cassiopeia.
(Raj:)And she was the mother of Andromeda,
who's over there.
(Howard:)Look, pretty stars.
This is her car, heh.
(Howard:)She hopes she can see you again
sometime.
Good, good. Uh...